<DPM-MESSAGE>
	<CLIENT-ID>decooda</CLIENT-ID>
	<TIMESTAMP>970-01-01T00:00:00Z</TIMESTAMP>
	<USER-NAME></USER-NAME>
	<PASSWORD></PASSWORD>
	<GUID></GUID>
	<RESULT-QUEUE>123456789.xyz</RESULT-QUEUE>
	<DPM-QUEUE></DPM-QUEUE>
	<PROCESS>
		<SEQ-STEP>
			<PLUGIN>
				<NAME>FIB</NAME>
				<SOURCE>DATA</SOURCE>
				<TARGET>DATA</TARGET>
			</PLUGIN>
		</SEQ-STEP>
	</PROCESS>
	<PAYLOAD>
		<DOCUMENT-ID>1289834</DOCUMENT-ID>
		<DOCUMENT-METADATA></DOCUMENT-METADATA>
		<DATA>	
		<![CDATA[		
				<div class="article"> 
					<h2 class="title"><a href="http://www.macrumors.com/2011/08/16/att-installing-4g-lte-network-equipment-in-apple-retail-stores/">AT&T Installing 4G LTE Network Equipment in Apple Retail Stores?</a></h2> 
					<div class="byline">Tuesday August 16, 2011 10:29 am PDT by Eric Slivka</div> 
					<div class="content"> 
						<img src="http://cdn.macrumors.com/article-new/2011/08/apple_store_lte_equipment.jpg" alt="" title="apple_store_lte_equipment" width="560" height="335" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-321176" />
<br/> 
Following up on the interest generated by <a href="http://www.macrumors.com/2011/08/15/carriers-testing-lte-enabled-iphone/">yesterday's disclosure</a> that wireless carriers are using a special build of iOS containing unique property list files referring to LTE compatibility, <a href="http://www.engadget.com/2011/08/16/why-is-lte-equipment-being-installed-in-an-apple-store/"><i>Engadget</i> now reports</a> that AT&T has recently installed LTE network equipment in at least one Apple retail store.<p class="quote">Now we've received the image you see above, which shows some 4G LTE equipment that was recently installed in a major Apple store -- by AT&T, according to our source. Making things somewhat more interesting is the equipment itself, one piece of which supports only the 700MHz and AWS bands -- both of which AT&T plans to use for its LTE network if the T-Mobile acquisition goes through.</p>Rumors have indicated that the iPhone 5 will be supporting the HSPA+ 4G standard, with Apple reportedly holding off on supporting the more advanced LTE 4G standard for the time being until adoption spreads and chips meeting Apple's size and performance standards become available early next year.
<br/> 

<br/> 
But with Apple providing its carrier partners with special iOS builds referencing LTE and carriers like AT&T apparently installing LTE equipment on-site at Apple stores, it seems natural to speculate that Apple is indeed testing LTE-enabled iPhones, perhaps in real-world settings.  The developments also provide hope for those seeking an LTE iPhone later this year, but the majority of reports continue to indicate that Apple will be holding off until 2012 to make the technology available to the public.
					</div> 
	
	
			Fortune Magazine reports that Deutsche Bank analyst Chris
			Whitmore today released a new research note claiming that Apple may
			be preparing to release two new iPhone models later this year with
			the usual iPhone revamp being joined by the debut of a cheaper model
			coming in at an unlocked, unsubsidized price of $349.
			
			Based on more than forty interviews with Jobs conducted over two years—as
			 well as interviews with more than a hundred family members, friends, 
			 adversaries, competitors, and colleagues—Walter Isaacson has written a 
			 riveting story of the roller-coaster life and searingly intense personality 
			 of a creative entrepreneur whose passion for perfection and ferocious drive 
			 revolutionized six industries: personal computers, animated movies, music, 
			 phones, tablet computing, and digital publishing.
			
			At a time when America is seeking ways to sustain its innovative edge, and 
			when societies around the world are trying to build digital-age economies, 
			Jobs stands as the ultimate icon of inventiveness and applied imagination. 
			He knew that the best way to create value in the twenty-first century was to 
			connect creativity with technology. He built a company where leaps of the 
			imagination were combined with remarkable feats of engineering.He built a company where leaps of the 
			imagination were combined with remarkable feats of engineering.
		]]>
		</DATA>
	</PAYLOAD>
</DPM-MESSAGE>